<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Michelle Meng&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Michelle Meng&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mimeng.art/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PC Financial - Points Tour</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/pc/</guid>
      <description>PC Financial wanted to find a fun way to engage the public to learn more about points and their products. We created a Beat the Shop Clock Game as a fixture of their Canada-wide points tour.
  CD: Amy Creyer
AD: Michelle Meng
CW: Sarah Sheppard</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBC</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/rbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/rbc/</guid>
      <description>The RBC eXperience store space is an unique RBC branch built to inspire innovation through special events and exhibits. For the eXperience space&amp;rsquo;s fall setup, we crafted a unique experience that explores the theme of life&amp;rsquo;s nonlinear journeys and milestones through colourful pathways and pinpoint motifs.
The storefront of the RBC eXperience store with the fall nonlinear journeys setup.
The window display using RBC-coloured ribbons and wooden pins to highlight milestone conversation starters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walkers</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/walkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/walkers/</guid>
      <description>Walkers wanted to help young adults cope with stress through humour and social media. We created the
It&amp;rsquo;s Ok to Potato campaign to tell hustling and stressed young adults that it&amp;rsquo;s OK to be a couch potato once in a while.
AD: Michelle Meng
CW: Sarah Sheppard</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Bumble</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/bumble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/bumble/</guid>
      <description>Finding a partner who eats like you is important in a relationship and it becomes harder if you have a restricted diet, like plant-based.
This is why popular plant-based option Beyond Meat is partnering with Bumble to help connect people with similar diets.
CW: Deryek Sandhu
AD: Michelle Meng</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lynwood Charlton Centre</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/lcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/lcc/</guid>
      <description>Mental health is important. Especially for our youth.
Lynwood Charlton Centre (LCC) is an organization committed to bettering the mental health of our youth, but their current branding doesn&amp;rsquo;t quite connect with their audience. This is where our re-branding comes in, to tell the youth that &amp;ldquo;we are here for you&amp;rdquo; in a more fun and friendly way.
  AD: Michelle Meng, Ashley Park</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotify Uncovered</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/spotify/</guid>
      <description>Spotify loves to use data to tell you about you. And data can tell us a lot about you. But data can’t show the feelings that music evokes.
Using Spotify Uncovered, you can document the music moments that data could never capture
AD: Michelle Meng, Katy van Nostrand</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wUfber</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/wufber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/wufber/</guid>
      <description>Since the pandemic, over 280, 000 dogs found new homes. But now with everyone going back to work, including Uber drivers, what happens to the dogs all alone at home? We created a new feature that lets Uber drivers bring their dogs to work and lets Uber riders experience the joy of riding with two best friends. This is Wufber.
  AD: Michelle Meng, Ashley Park
CW: Mnrupe Virk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touchland Palm Reader</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/touchland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/touchland/</guid>
      <description>To prove to the world that there is a way to sanitize without harsh chemicals harming your hands, Touchland reads your palms’ cracked, dry past, and enlightens you with hydrating scents designed to be better care for your hands.
  AD: Michelle Meng
CW: Sarah Sheppard</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>