<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Michelle Meng&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Michelle Meng&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mimeng.art/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wendy&#39;s The Unbinging</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work10/</guid>
      <description>AD: Michelle Meng
CW: Deryek Sandhu, Ashley Park
Due to shortage of beef for Wendy&amp;rsquo;s during COVID 19, we explored a way to target a new consumer group for Wendy&amp;rsquo;s: fitness and diet beginners. We explore the economic behaviors of Temptation Coupling and Fresh Start Effect: vaccine is coming out soon, meaning quarantine is almost over, so it&amp;rsquo;s time to start fresh and get moving in a sustainable, unbinging way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix &amp; Nom</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work2/</guid>
      <description>One of our favorite evening rituals is watching Netflix, while munching on something. Introducing Netflix &amp;amp; Nom, the duo you didn&amp;rsquo;t think you need in your night routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Car Concept</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:44:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work3/</guid>
      <description>Combining &amp;ldquo;Dog&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Car&amp;rdquo; comes up with thousands of possibilities in my imagination. Below are three ideas that popped into my head as I contemplated these two words:
Mini Dalmatian Cooper &amp;ldquo;Mini Dalmatian Cooper&amp;rdquo; that is perfect for dog lovers who want a unique touch to a mini cooper:
Woofer Application &amp;ldquo;Woofer Application&amp;rdquo; an in-city rideshare that is convenient for dog lovers to request rides for their dogs:
Smart Shiba Car &amp;ldquo;Smart Shiba Car&amp;rdquo; an upstanding Shiba that transforms into a smart car with a push of a button:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magik Soda Concept</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:50:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work4/</guid>
      <description>The brand “Magik Soda” comes from the word “magic”, as this line of soft drink is inspired by the idea of “magic potions”. Hence the unique glass bottle shapes, and the colour changing flavours induced by the juice capsules. The names of each of the flavours were inspired by times of the day, &amp;ldquo;Sunrise Waves&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Midday Watermelon&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Sunset Dreams&amp;rdquo;.
Sunrise Waves Midday Watermelon Sunset Dreams Promotional Campaign </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SO:yA Media Kit</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work6/</guid>
      <description>SO:yA is a new Montreal Vegan bakery whose goal is to make delicious Vegan desserts accessible to all. This media kit book was made to provide the owner with the online and offline media tools that she will need in order to successfully launch her new business in her unique way.
                              .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix: Streaming with Strangers</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:56:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work5/</guid>
      <description>The new normal is staying at home, and it can get a bit lonely. Now Netflix lets you stream with strangers without any of the dangers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women Empowerment Posters</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work7/</guid>
      <description>This was a series of posters for the Women Empowerment Expo in Shanghai in 2015.
These posters explore the themes of self identity as females individuals and the themes of the complexity of the female mind.
He For She Poster The first poster explores the representation of the female and male mind alike with the colorful blocks each meaning &amp;ldquo;feelings&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;rationality&amp;rdquo;, etc. This poster is signaling men and women alike supporting the empowerment of women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>L&#39;Oreal Soy Cycle App Concept</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work8/</guid>
      <description>This was an application made for the 2019 L&amp;rsquo;Oreal Brandstorm competition.
Our team researched for a biodegradable material that could replace the current plastic production, and we came across: Soy Plastic. From then on, our whole case competition is built on branding the concept of switching to soy plastic. Also we wanted the consumer to adopt the behavior of recycling product plastic within the Garnier L&amp;rsquo;Oreal ecosystem, to finally replace all plastic that they use to Soy plastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memories of Michelle</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/work9/</guid>
      <description>An Album Cover made in Procreate dedicated to my university graduation.
This sunset captured my favorite area of Montreal, the Plateau. This brings me memories of every beginning of the semester, where I can walk around this area with my friends. I wanted to layer this on top of the letter background, as if the figure previously is staring into the sunset, which represents my fondest memories.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>