<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Michelle Meng&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Michelle Meng&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mimeng.art/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Binging Lingo</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/duo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/duo/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to learning anything, we learn better when we are entertained and engaged. So, Duolingo is bringing language learning to young adult’s favourite form of entertainment: TV shows.
Introducing Binginglingo: the Duolingo partnership with Netflix that along with early access to a popular Netflix series, lets users binge their favourite shows, and learn a language. All at the same time.
CW: Zac Smith AD: Michelle Meng</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coors Flight</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/coors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/coors/</guid>
      <description>Work from home. What was supposed to be the saviour to early mornings and outfit indecision has created longer working hours and declining mental health. When we finally step away from our Slack pings and Zoom calls, we transition to an even tinier screen - our cellphones.
Coors sees this and wants to remind you to disconnect with a Coors fLight
CW: Deryek Sandhu, Jonathan Choong AD: Michelle Meng, Ashley Park</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Play</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/lego/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/lego/</guid>
      <description>Kids are overscheduled. Even “play” needs to be scheduled into the day now. To show the importance of &amp;ldquo;play&amp;rdquo;, LEGO creates a new time on the clock**.** They’re taking away “5:00 PM” to make it &amp;ldquo;PL:AY PM&amp;rdquo;, and putting “PLAY” back on the agenda, literally.
  AD: Michelle Meng, Tricia Rego, Keshia Enns, Anna Jenkins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lynwood Charlton Centre</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/lcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/lcc/</guid>
      <description>The Lynwood Charlton Centre (LCC) is a modern, forward-thinking organization, committed to helping children &amp;amp; youth, but there is a disconnect with their branding and messaging.
A more fun &amp;amp; current rebranding project is needed to help LCC reach prospective patients in a more engaging way.
AD: Michelle Meng, Ashley Park</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Bumble</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/bumble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/bumble/</guid>
      <description>Plant-based diets are growing in popularity but can lead to some challenges when it comes to dating. For plant-based eaters, it&amp;rsquo;s especially difficult to find a partner who eats like them.
To make life easier, Beyond Meat is partnering with Bumble to help plant-based eaters match with each other.
CW: Deryek Sandhu AD: Michelle Meng</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotify Unwrapped</title>
      <link>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mimeng.art/portfolio/spotify/</guid>
      <description>Spotify loves to use data to tell you about you. And data can tell us a lot about you. But data is just that- statistics and numbers; cold, hard facts.
Using Spotify Unwrapped, you can document the music moments that data could never capture.
AD: Michelle Meng, Katy van Nostrand</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>